{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Which flagg has white on it?",
      "rightAnswer": "Laos",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Congo-brazzaville", "Gabon", "Kamerun"]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Which flagg has red on it?",
      "rightAnswer": "Kenya",
      "wrongAnswers": ["India", "Cyprus", "Bhutan"]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which flagg has green on it?",
      "rightAnswer": "Pakistan",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Iraq", "Cape verde", "Armenia"]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which flagg has stars on it?",
      "rightAnswer": "Philippines",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Kuwait", "Bahrain", "Cambodja"]
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which flagg has just stripes on it?",
      "rightAnswer": "Saudiarabia",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Yemen", "Indonesia", "Ukraine"]
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which flagg has hands on it?",
      "rightAnswer": "Brunei",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Nepal", "Mongolia", "North korea"]
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Which flagg has a circle on it?",
      "rightAnswer": "Bangladesh",
      "wrongAnswers": ["United arab emirates", "Myanmar", "Qatar"]
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Which flagg has an animal on it?",
      "rightAnswer": "Dominica",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Micronesia", "Marshall islands", "Palau"]
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which flagg has a weapon on it?",
      "rightAnswer": "Mozambique",
      "wrongAnswers": ["Georgia", "Lebanon", "Syria"]
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Which flagg has a moon on it?",
      "rightAnswer": "Maldives",
      "wrongAnswers": ["China", "Vietnam", "East timor"]
    }
  ]
}
